So to summarize the main points one very important thing is
所以总结一下要点，非常重要的一点是
that the activation record has to be designed together with the code generation.
激活记录必须与代码生成一起设计。
So you have to do these things at the same time. You can't just design the
所以你必须同时做这些事情。你不能仅仅设计
activation record without thinking about what code you're going to generate And
激活记录，而不用考虑要生成什么代码
you can't just think about generating code without making some decisions about where
您不能只考虑生成代码，而不决定在何处生成代码
the data is going to be lived. So the code and the data it manipulates, have
数据将会是真实的。所以代码和它操作的数据
to be designed simultaneously. Code generation can be done by a recursive traversal
要同时设计。代码生成可以通过递归遍历来完成
of the abstract syntax street, so just like type checking. Cogeneration can
抽象语法街，所以就像类型检查一样。热电联产可以
be expressed as a r ecursive tree-walk And that's a very handy way to think about
被表达为一种令人厌烦的树木漫步，这是一种非常方便的方式来思考
cogeneration because it allows you to think about one case at a time without having
热电联产，因为它允许您一次考虑一个案例，而不需要
to get mixed up thinking about all the different constructs at one time. >> And
把一次考虑所有不同的结构搞混了。>>和
finally I recommend that you use a stack machine for your compiler. So if you're
最后，我建议您在编译器中使用堆栈机器。所以如果你是
implementing a course project, the stack machine is the simplest discipline and
实施一个课程项目，堆叠机是最简单的学科
it gives you a nice framework for think, for breaking up the project into manageable
它为您提供了一个很好的思考框架，可以将项目分解成可管理的
pieces. And because of that simplicity, I think it's a really good way
碎片。由于这种简单性，我认为这是一种非常好的方式
to learn about writing compilers. Now, it is important to realize that production compilers
学习如何编写编译器。现在，重要的是要认识到产生式编译器
do, do some different things. They're not quite as simple as, the stack
做，做一些不同的事情。它们并不像堆栈那样简单
machine cogeneration that we have outlined in the last few videos. So, the main differences,
我们在最后几个视频中概述的机器热电联产。所以，主要的不同之处在于，
or, or, the main difference, is that the big emphasis in a production compiler
或者，或者说，主要的区别在于，在生产编译器中最重要的是
is on keeping values and registers. It's much more efficient to do
就是保存价值和记录。这样做效率要高得多
operations out of registers than to be saving and loading values from the stack And
寄存器外的操作，而不是从堆栈中保存和加载值
so, especially the values in the current activation record or current stack
所以，特别是当前激活记录或当前堆栈中的值
frame. It, in production compiler we try to keep those in registers instead of on the
画框。在生产编译器中，我们尝试将这些内容保存在寄存器中，而不是放在
stack And also, typically a pressure compiler, to the extent that it has to use
堆栈，并且通常是压力编译器，在一定程度上它必须使用
temporaries, in the activation record. These would be resolved, laid out directly
临时的，在激活记录中。这些都会被解决，直接列出
in the activation record, not pushed and popped from the stack. That means they'd be
在激活记录中，不从堆栈推送和弹出。那就意味着他们会
assigned, pre-assigned locations in the activation record, just like, the function
激活记录中已分配的、预先分配的位置，就像函数一样
arguments in the simple language we looked at are assigned fixed positions in the activation
我们看到的简单语言中的参数在激活中被分配了固定的位置
record. So those temporary values would also be assigned fixed positions,
录音。所以这些临时值也会被分配固定位置，
so you could save the trouble of manipulating the stack pointer.
因此，您可以省去操作堆栈指针的麻烦。